JEAN SUSOR

FRONTEND DEVELOPER



SUMMARY

I'm currently working freelance as a Web Developer. I can do backend using NodeJS but I am more comfortable working as Frontend Angular Developer. Previously, I always worked with a team so I'm already used to Git's Version Control. I am a team player and can communicate effectively.

As a Wordpress Administrator before, I know a website's best practices, SEO, design to enhance customer satisfaction and to high rank in Google.



CONTACT

Phone Email

0917080622 jlalama2011@gmail.com

Address

101, 97633, Dúbravica, Slovakia

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jean-susor/

Github

https://github.com/Puffyfish



EDUCATION

Mar 2023 Angular

Udemy

Jan 2022 Web Development

Udemy

April 2017 Web Designing

Informatics Computer Technology

2005 - 2009 BS Nursing

Cebu Normal University



TECH STACK

- HTML
- Angular
- ExpressJS

- CSS
- NodeJS
- MongoDB

- Javascript
- Typescript



PROJECTS

Report App

April 2023

HtML, SCSS, Javascript, Angular, MySql, PHP

- Overall design of website using Angular Material
- Landing page which was created with CSS
- Integration of frontend to backend
- Creating the components for the individual pages

To-do App

April 2023

HtML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Angular Material

- basic to-do app that has to-do lists per project
- · overall design of the app using Angular Material
- · creating database using json-server

Dashboard Website

Sep 2022

Javascript, MongoDB, ExpressJS, NodeJS

-won first place in W3Schools 2021 Challenge

- · Overall design
- Responsible for CRUD operations of data
- · Setting the routes using ExpressJS
- Demonstrating data using ChartJS
- Managing MongDB to handle data

Recipe Website

June 2022

HtML, CSS, Javascript -won third place in W3Schools 2021 Challenge

- · overall design of website
- popup feature of recipes

JEAN SUSOR

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Wordpress Website Manager Lab41 2020 - 2021

Enhanced and tracked different websites' SEO, design, content to rank top in Google.

Warehouse Admin Staff Chef Direct, Booker Group 2016 - 2018

I managed ingoing and outgoing deliveries using the company's CRM, organized receipts and paperworks for proper documentation and responded accordingly to problems.

Stock Control Administrator

2014-2016

Kreemar Enterprises

I tracked daily business operations through a CRM. I communicated with main suppliers, and created monthly reports of profits and expenditures

➤ Staff Nurse 2013

Vicente Sotto Memorial Medical Center

I was a staff nurse assigned in 4 different areas in rotation: Operating Room, Emergency Room, Medical Ward, OB ward.

JEAN SUSOR

FRONTEND DEVELOPER





Certificate no: UC-13fc8520-4a26-4ab3-afe1-195b9fe6bccb
Certificate url: ude.my/UC-13fc8520-4a26-4ab3-afe1-195b9fe6bccb
Reference Number: 0004

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

Angular - The Complete Guide (2023 Edition)

Instructors Maximilian Schwarzmüller

Jean Ialaine Susor

Date March 26, 2023 Length 34.5 total hours





CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

This certifies that

Jean Susor

has completed the necessary courses of study and passed the W3Schools' JavaScript exams and is hereby declared a

Certified JavaScript Developer

with fundamental knowledge of web development using JavaScript and the HTML DOM.

Issued March 15, 2023

Thomas Thorsell-Arntsen for W3schools.com

Verify completion at https://verify.w3schools.com/1NIDVYAYGT